export const questions = [
  {
    question: "How can I use the Amarabelliana system to select attire?",
    answer:
      "The customer can browse and select their desired attire. The system offers two advanced technologies: AI and 3D. The 3D mannequin model allows customers to visualize their selected attire based on the selected body structure and skin tone of their mannequin. Meanwhile, AI offers visualization based on the customer’s desired design.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I visit an Amarabelliana branch for in-person fittings?",
    answer:
      "Yes, customers can directly go to the nearest Amarabelliana branch if they prefer to choose and do their fittings in person.",
  },
  {
    question: "Where are Amarabelliana’s branches located?",
    answer:
      "Amarabelliana has four operating branches located in Northgate, Tigbi, Pillar Village, and Negros Occidental.",
  },
  {
    question: "How are size and measurements taken at Amarabelliana?",
    answer:
      "We take exact measurements in inches and follow a specific sequence. For men, it involves the back bone, chest, waistline, tummy, sleeve length, and armhole. For women, it includes the back, bust line, waistline at the navel, figure shoulder to bust, bust to navel, and length depending on the heels they will wear.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the estimated measurements for men’s and women’s attire?",
    answer:
      "Small: 26 inches waistline, Medium: 28 inches to 29 inches, Large: 30 inches to 32 inches, XL: 34 inches to 36 inches, 2XL to 3XL: Followed by",
  },
  {
    question: "What payment methods are accepted?",
    answer:
      "We accept Gcash and over-the-counter payments.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the policy for delivery and return?",
    answer:
      "Pick up is 2 days before use, and return is 2 days after use. There is no cancellation, but rescheduling for pickup or changing of the rented attire is allowed. Late returns will incur a penalty charged on a per-day basis.",
  },
  {
    question: "What happens if an item is damaged?",
    answer:
      "If the attire is damaged, the valid ID of the customer will be held until the damaged attire is fixed at the customer’s expense.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I book or reserve attire?",
    answer:
      "For bookings, the customer can proceed to payment and the rental process. For reservations, the customer will pay a reservation fee and discuss a specific date for booking. If the customer is unable to decide on that day, the reservation will be forfeited.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the cancellation and refund policy?",
    answer:
      "Cancellation of renting attire is not allowed and is non-refundable.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I request a virtual consultation?",
    answer:
      "Customers can request a scheduled appointment by reaching out through our end-to-end message service.",
  },
]